iloveim.com 2010-06-23

# ILoveIM.com Web Messenger (MSN, Yahoo, AOL, GTalk)

IloveIM, LLC ("ILoveIM") is committed to helping you protect your privacy and developing technology to help protect the safety. This Privacy Statement applies to [www.iloveim.com](http://www.iloveim.com/) and all its sub-domains ("Websites") that runs ILoveIM web-based instant messenger application and governs data collection and its usage. 

ILoveIM, LLC is a Participant in the **TRUSTe Privacy Seal Program**. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to advance privacy and trust in the networked world. As this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices monitored for compliance by TRUSTe. This Privacy policy covers the web site [www.iloveim.com](http://www.iloveim.com/). 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at **privacy@iloveim.com** . If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns. 

**COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
ILoveIM do not require users to provide personally identifiable information to visit the Websites. However, in order to use of certain features users may need to provide some personally identifiable information. 

  * _Third party IM network login and password._ ILoveIM allows you to access third party instant messenger networks by logging into your account through ILoveIM. In order to access your 3rd party IM network account, you need to enter applicable login and password information on ILoveIM Website. ILoveIM does not store your password from 3rd party IM network accounts, but your login name may be stored.
  * _Third party IM networks._ ILoveIM may receive personal information about you from a 3rd party IM network that you access through ILoveIM. This information usually includes, but not limited to the following - User's IM network display name, Avatar/Display Picture, Contacts list, User and contacts profile details, Status information. ILoveIM does not store any of this information and uses it according to this Privacy Policy when provides service for you.
  * _Communication Data and Chat Messages._ ILoveIM does not collect your communication data and/or chat messages that were sent/received during your usage of ILoveIM Websites. The history of your chat messages is not stored on any kind of persistence storage and being deleted from a server memory (RAM) at this moment you leave ILoveIM Websites.
  * _ILoveIM Usage Data._ ILoveIM may collect some usage data based on the usage of ILoveIM Websites and its features. This does not include any personally identifiable information with the exception of IP addresses (see "IP Addresses" section below).
  * _Third party Applications._ ILoveIM may enter into agreements with third party developers ("Developers") to make their applications available through ILoveIM Websites. In order to enable these applications to run, ILoveIM may need to provide them some personal identifiable information that is related to a service provided by applications. ILoveIM requires Developers to use this information only to provide the application and do not share your personal information with anybody. Developers are solely responsible for complying with their own privacy policy.
  * _ILoveIM WhiteLabel._ ILoveIM provides its WhiteLabel product that allows third parties to run web-based messenger service under their brand name (not affiliated with ILoveIM). ILoveIM hosts and runs WhiteLabel application on its own servers, but WhiteLabel partners are allowed to host the home page which is being used for the login purposes. In this case WhiteLabel partners may get access to your personal identifiable information such as third party IM networks login/password details. ILoveIM Privacy Policy link is displayed only on the WhiteLabel sites that are completely hosted and controlled by ILoveIM. WhiteLaber partners are solely responsible for complying with their own privacy policy.
  * _Demographic information and Surveys._ ILoveIM may ask users to participate on some surveys to collect demographic information about Website visitors. Surveys are provided by third party company - [www.CrowdScience.com](http://www.crowdscience.com/) that does not store any personally identifiable information. Their complete privacy policy is available on <http://www.crowdscience.com/privacy>

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. ILoveIM uses cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file (see following link for more details - <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>).

ILoveIM may set a persistent cookie to store your passwords and/or login information, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Our advertisement partners may also use cookies in order to present you with targeted offers and track the ads performance.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

**Web Beacons**  
Websites and any communications sent by the Websites may contain electronic images (generally, single-pixel ".gif" images) called "web beacons." These web beacons allow ILoveIM and third parties to monitor and collect certain information about the viewer of the web page, web-based document, e-mail message or other communication, such as the type of browser requesting the web beacon, the Device Identifier of the device that the web beacon is sent to and the time the web beacon was viewed. ILoveIM may use web beacons on its Websites, include, without limitation, the following: 

  * Counting unique users (actually, unique web browsers), visits and page views. 
  * Monitoring traffic and conversion patterns through our various product and service offerings on the Websites. For example, web beacons may be integrated into a merchandise product page as well as the subsequent shopping cart, transaction and verification pages.
  * Personalizing your experience when you visit the Web Sites, including the advertising and content you see.
  * Determining whether or not messages were opened, links were clicked or notifications/offers were acted upon.

**IP Addresses**  
User's IP addresses may be collected by ILoveIM for administrative and analytical needs. ILoveIM uses IP addresses log in order to build internal analytics reports of the geographical locations of its users. 

**THIRD-PARTY AD SERVING & AUDIENCE AND TRAFFIC MEASUREMENT**  
ILoveIM may use third party network advertisers to serve advertisements on the Websites and may use a traffic measurement service to analyze traffic on the Websites. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to the Websites and other web sites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Although advertisers and other companies do not have access to cookies set by the Wesites, the Websites' third party ad network providers, the advertisers, the sponsors, and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have cookies enabled in your browser. These third party cookies are set to, among other things, help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in, to prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements are to you. Note that any images (or any other parts of a web page) served by third parties in association with third party cookies may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities. Third party cookies and web beacons are governed by each third party's specific privacy policy, not this one. 

**THIRD PARTY COOKIES**  
The use of cookies by third party partners is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. It is not required to allow third party cookies to use our web site. You can disable third party cookies in your browser at your will. See below for details - <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie#Privacy_and_third-party_cookies>

**WITH WHOM INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED**  
Except as otherwise disclosed at the time you provide your information, the following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others: 

**Third parties providing services on our behalf**  
ILoveIM may employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf; examples include hosting or operating Websites, data analysis, marketing assistance and customer service. These third parties may have access to your personal information for the purpose of performing such functions on the Websites' behalf. 

**Non-Personal Information**  
ILoveIM may share non-personal information, such as aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and web site usage information with third parties. 

**Products and Services Offered in Partnership with Third-Party(s)**  
Certain Web Sites are provided to you in partnership with third party(s) ("Co-Branded Sites") and may require you to disclose personal information in order to register for and access products and/or services. Such Co-Branded Sites will identify the third party partner(s). If you elect to register for such products and/or services at Co-Branded Sites you may be providing your information to both Company and the third party partner(s) and your information may be subject to a separate privacy policy available at the point of registration. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave the ILoveIM website you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as ILoveIM. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to an ILoveIM site, you should read that site's privacy statement before providing any personally identifiable information. 

**Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions**  
ILoveIM may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions through the Websites that may require registration. If you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion, your personal information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion. 

Please note that ILoveIM does not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with third parties for their promotional purposes without your acceptance to enter a sweepstake, contest or other promotion.

**Legal Protections and Law Enforcement**  
We may disclose information about our users, including your personal information, in the event we are required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or other valid law enforcement measures; to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Websites and applicable laws; or to protect the legal rights, interests, or safety of the Websites, our users or others. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you. 

**Security of your Personal Information**  
ILoveIM Web Instant Messenger Service is committed to helping protect the security of the personal information you provide. Personal information we collect is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access, and we use a variety of technologies and procedures to help protect this information from loss or misuse, and from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

**CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We do not collect any personal information except your login, password and IP address; there is no access available on our site to update this information. 

**A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY**  
ILoveIM does not knowingly collect any personal information from children younger than the age of thirteen (13) on the Websites and we will delete any information later determined to be from a user younger than thirteen (13). 

**CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the ILoveIM home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by means of a notice on our home page.

ILoveIM, LLC  
18 Edelweiss ct.  
Voorhees, NJ 08043 

[Last Updated: April 27th 2009]
